Guide to the Stanford University Commencement Collection SC1020
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Audiovisual materials, 1937-2013; Series 3
  - 119th annual commencement, 2010-06-13
    - UN Amb. Susan Rice, 2010-06-13; 10-0613-2 (Box 5)
  - 121st annual commencement, 2012; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
    - Commencement, 2012, 2012-06-17 (Box 5)
  - 122nd annual commencement, 2013
    - Ceremony, 2013 Jun 16; Accession ARCH.2014-064; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 3)
    - Ceremony, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
  - 123rd annual commencement, 2014
    - Ceremony, 2014-06-15; sc1020_s3_2014.1; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
- Additional materials, 1892-2010; Series 4
  - 12th Annual Commencement
    - "Consolatio: A Memorial Ode" (Ode in memory of those members of the Class of Nineteen Hundred and Three of Stanford University who died during the month of their graduation, by Raymond Macdonald Alden, 1903 May 25; Accession ARCH.2014-065 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 122nd Annual Commencement
    - Marshall ribbon, 2013 Jun 16; Accession ARCH.2014-064 (Box 1, Folder 2)